<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Top Cars</string>
    <string name="title_onboard">All information about cars in one place</string>
    <string name="desc_onboard">Here you will find comprehensive information about thousands of car models - from characteristics and technical data to prices and reviews. Choosing a new car or being interested in the characteristics of an existing one, we have everything you need.</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="added">Added</string>
    <string name="test">test</string>
    <string name="deleted">Deleted</string>
    <string name="search_car">Search car</string>
    <string name="tesla">Tesla</string>
    <string name="model_s">Model S</string>
    <string name="t_desc1">Luxury electric car with cutting-edge technology and impressive performance. It offers spacious interiors and a long driving range. Model S is known for its sleek design and top-notch features.</string>
    <string name="t_desc2">Affordable electric car designed for everyday use. It combines efficiency with advanced features like Autopilot. Model 3 is a practical choice for those looking to transition to electric driving.</string>
    <string name="model_3">Model 3</string>
    <string name="t_desc3">Electric SUV with distinctive falcon-wing doors. It provides ample seating and versatile cargo space. Model X is perfect for families and adventure enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="t_desc4">Compact electric SUV that offers a blend of practicality and Tesla\'s signature technology. Model Y delivers a comfortable and eco-friendly driving experience.</string>
    <string name="t_desc5">Electric sports car that redefined performance. It accelerates like a rocket and has a stunning design. Roadster is a true icon of electric supercars.</string>
    <string name="t_desc6">Electric pickup truck with a futuristic, rugged design. It\'s built for strength and durability. Cybertruck represents a bold step in the evolution of utility vehicles.</string>
    <string name="t_desc7">Electric semi-truck designed for freight hauling. It\'s efficient, safe, and has autonomous driving capabilities. Semi Truck is transforming the logistics industry.</string>
    <string name="t_desc8">Concept car that showcases Tesla\'s vision for the future of electric mobility. It\'s packed with innovative features and represents a leap forward in sustainable transportation.</string>
    <string name="t_desc9">Concept car that represents Tesla\'s commitment to sustainable transportation and cutting-edge design. Model B is a glimpse into the future of eco-conscious mobility.</string>
    <string name="t_desc10">Concept car with a focus on next-generation technology and eco-friendly materials. Model C is designed to lead the way in environmentally friendly transportation.</string>
    <string name="model_x">Model X</string>
    <string name="model_y">Model Y</string>
    <string name="roadster">Roadster</string>
    <string name="cybertruck">Cybertruck</string>
    <string name="semi_truck">Semi Truck</string>
    <string name="model_a">Model A</string>
    <string name="model_b">Model B</string>
    <string name="model_c">Model C</string>
    <string name="ferrari">Ferrari</string>
    <string name="ferrari_488_gtb">Ferrari 488 GTB</string>
    <string name="f_desc1">The Ferrari 488 GTB is a high-performance sports car known for its breathtaking speed and agility. It\'s powered by a twin-turbo V8 engine that delivers exhilarating performance on both the road and the track. With its iconic styling and precise handling, the 488 GTB is a true Ferrari masterpiece.</string>
    <string name="f_desc2">The Ferrari Portofino is a grand touring convertible that combines luxury and performance. Its retractable hardtop roof allows you to enjoy open-air driving while maintaining the elegance and comfort of a GT car. The Portofino\'s V8 engine provides a thrilling driving experience, making it a perfect choice for long journeys.</string>
    <string name="f_desc3">The Ferrari F8 Tributo is a supercar that embodies the essence of Italian automotive excellence. It features a powerful V8 engine that propels it to incredible speeds, and its aerodynamic design ensures optimal performance. With cutting-edge technology and a driver-focused cockpit, the F8 Tributo offers an unforgettable driving experience.</string>
    <string name="f_desc4">The Ferrari GTC4Lusso is a grand tourer designed for the discerning driver who seeks both style and practicality. Its V12 engine delivers a harmonious blend of power and refinement, making it a versatile choice for long-distance journeys. The GTC4Lusso\'s four-seat configuration and spacious interior ensure comfort for all occupants.</string>
    <string name="f_desc5">The Ferrari 812 Superfast is a V12 coupe that lives up to its name with blistering acceleration and top speed. Its aggressive design and commanding presence on the road are complemented by a luxurious interior. The 812 Superfast is a true supercar that offers an unmatched driving experience.</string>
    <string name="f_desc6">The Ferrari Roma is a 2+2 sports car that combines timeless elegance with modern performance. Its sleek and sophisticated design pays homage to the brand\'s iconic heritage. With a powerful V8 engine and advanced technology, the Roma offers a perfect balance of style and speed.</string>
    <string name="f_desc7">The Ferrari SF90 Stradale is a hybrid hypercar that represents the future of automotive engineering. It combines a V8 engine with electric motors to deliver mind-boggling power and efficiency. The SF90 Stradale showcases Ferrari\'s commitment to innovation and sustainability.</string>
    <string name="f_desc8">The Ferrari LaFerrari is a limited-edition hypercar that pushes the boundaries of performance. With a hybrid powertrain and cutting-edge aerodynamics, it\'s a masterpiece of engineering. The LaFerrari is a symbol of exclusivity and automotive excellence.</string>
    <string name="f_desc9">The Ferrari Enzo is a legendary supercar that pays tribute to the brand\'s founder. Its V12 engine and advanced technology make it a formidable performer on the track. The Enzo is a collector\'s dream and a symbol of Ferrari\'s racing heritage.</string>
    <string name="f_desc10">The Ferrari Testarossa is an iconic sports car that defined an era. Its distinctive side strakes and powerful flat-12 engine made it an instant classic. The Testarossa continues to captivate enthusiasts with its timeless design and thrilling performance.</string>
    <string name="ferrari_portofino">Ferrari Portofino</string>
    <string name="ferrari_f8_tributo">Ferrari F8 Tributo</string>
    <string name="ferrari_gtc4lusso">Ferrari GTC4Lusso</string>
    <string name="ferrari_812_superfast">Ferrari 812 Superfast</string>
    <string name="ferrari_roma">Ferrari Roma</string>
    <string name="ferrari_sf90_stradale">Ferrari SF90 Stradale</string>
    <string name="ferrari_laferrari">Ferrari LaFerrari</string>
    <string name="ferrari_enzo">Ferrari Enzo</string>
    <string name="ferrari_testarossa">Ferrari Testarossa</string>
    <string name="bmw">BMW</string>
    <string name="bmw_3_series">BMW 3 Series</string>
    <string name="b_desc1">The BMW 3 Series is a luxury compact car that sets the standard for performance and style in its class. Known for its precise handling and strong engine options, it offers a dynamic driving experience. The 3 Series combines elegance with athleticism, making it a favorite among enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="b_desc2">The BMW 5 Series is an executive sedan that excels in comfort and technology. With a spacious and well-appointed interior, it caters to both driver and passengers. The 5 Series is a symbol of sophistication and sophistication on the road.</string>
    <string name="b_desc3">The BMW X3 is a compact luxury SUV that offers versatility and performance. It combines a plush cabin with agile handling, making it a versatile choice for urban and off-road adventures. The X3 is a well-rounded SUV that meets the demands of modern drivers.</string>
    <string name="b_desc4">The BMW X5 is a midsize luxury SUV that brings together luxury and utility. It boasts a spacious interior, advanced technology features, and a comfortable ride. The X5 is a premium SUV that offers both style and substance.</string>
    <string name="b_desc5">The BMW 7 Series is a full-size luxury sedan that redefines opulence. With a sumptuous interior, advanced tech amenities, and powerful engine options, it caters to those who demand the best. The 7 Series represents the pinnacle of BMW\'s craftsmanship and innovation.</string>
    <string name="b_desc6">The BMW M3 is a high-performance sedan that delivers exhilarating power and precision handling. It\'s a true sports car in a sedan\'s clothing, designed for driving enthusiasts. The M3 is a perfect blend of everyday usability and track-ready performance.</string>
    <string name="b_desc7">The BMW M5 is a high-performance sports sedan that offers uncompromising power and agility. With a potent V8 engine and advanced chassis tuning, it accelerates and handles like a sports car. The M5 represents the pinnacle of BMW\'s M Division.</string>
    <string name="b_desc8">The BMW i3 is an electric city car that reimagines urban mobility. Its futuristic design and eco-friendly powertrain make it a sustainable choice. The i3 is perfect for city dwellers looking for an emission-free driving experience.</string>
    <string name="b_desc9">The BMW i8 is a plug-in hybrid sports car that combines cutting-edge technology with striking design. It offers exhilarating performance and the convenience of electric driving. The i8 is a symbol of BMW\'s commitment to sustainable sports cars.</string>
    <string name="b_desc10">The BMW Z4 is a sports convertible that embodies the joy of open-air driving. Its dynamic handling and spirited engine options make it a thrill to drive. The Z4 is a roadster designed for those who appreciate the freedom of the open road.</string>
    <string name="bmw_5_series">BMW 5 Series</string>
    <string name="bmw_x3">BMW X3</string>
    <string name="bmw_x5">BMW X5</string>
    <string name="bmw_7_series">BMW 7 Series</string>
    <string name="bmw_m3">BMW M3</string>
    <string name="bmw_m5">BMW M5</string>
    <string name="bmw_i3">BMW i3</string>
    <string name="bmw_i8">BMW i8</string>
    <string name="bmw_z4">BMW Z4</string>
    <string name="all">All</string>
</resources>